♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we’ve got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright
on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we’ll
withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there
when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we
will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko
stronger after all ♪
(SINISTER MUSIC)
Hello? Is anyone there?
What?
Misses Hertz caught us red-handed.
She made us give up our cell phones.
(BUZZING)
(YAWNS)
Hey, you really look wiped out.
What did you do last night?
I worked on a little program.
An advanced research engine of sorts.
It’s a browser which I’m
trying to make to help Aelita
look for more info on
materialization in the Lyoko towers.
Just imagine all the things
she’s gonna learn when she gets here.
She’s gonna be amazed.
I think about it all the time.
I can’t wait for that day to come.
Yeah. It’s gonna…it’s gonna be great.
Hi, Ulrich.
Hello.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
Okay, guys. It’s time for us
to work up a sweat.
So long, Yumi.
Yumi, w-wait, I…
Yes?
I, um…
Are you okay?
Well, yeah? Why are you asking?
I just, uh, just…asked.
See you later.
Okay.
Ulrich, move it, huh!
“Ulrich, I don’t know
how to tell you this, so I’m writing it.
“I’ve always admired you.
“I’ve been wanting to tell you for ages,
but I didn’t have the nerve.
“Also, I wasn’t 100 percent sure,
but now I am. I love you.
Signed, Yumi.”
(LAUGHS)
Ulrich, watch out!
Ulrich, are you okay?
How could that have happened?
Uh, hey, Ulrich, don’t take this badly,
but your playing was kinda weird.
You can say that again!
Why, even Jeremie was
better than you today!
My mind wasn’t on the game.
Lay off, huh?
No way!
He’ll lay off as soon as you
tell us what’s wrong.
It’s just that…
Well, I got this letter from a girl.
The kind of letter
a girl sends when she’s…
He’s in love!
(LAUGHS)
Ulrich’s in love!
That’s the problem. I’m not in love.
I’m…I’m not sure I am.
I can’t even manage to talk to her.
And can you tell us
who the lucky lady is?
You’ve gotta be kidding.
I’m not telling anyone.
One more thing--
not a word to Yumi.
I don’t want this to get around.
Uh…
Hey, Odd, did I really play
better than him?
Milly or Tamiya?
No, they’re too young.
Claire.
Sandra?
No, no, much too young.
And they’re so, you know, they’re…
they’re too uptight.
Emily! Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, it’s her!
Look, I’m an expert with girls.
She’s pretty,
she’s the outdoors type,
she’s the one who flipped for him.
Oh, yeah? Who is Emily flipped over?
It’s Jim! Emily’s crazy about Jim.
Jim? You’re kidding.
Well, they say that love is blind.
Oh! I’m, uh, I’m s-sorry.
(BARKS)
(WHIMPERS)
Kiwi?
Who did that to you?
(BUZZING)
Come on, run!
Kiwi!
He doesn’t look well at all.
You think it’s serious?
Don’t worry, Odd.
He’ll be back on his feet in no time.
I mean, back on his paws.
(KNOCKING)
I brought some pills
and antivenom compresses.
Thanks, Yumi. Come in.
This’ll make you feel better.
Uh, Yumi? Come over here, please.
I wanted to tell you something.
I did, too.
They say Emily’s in love with Jim!
With Jim?
Odd told me all about it. Weird, huh?
I’ve got class now. See ya!
Hey, what’s that all about, huh?
I don’t know!
And then I heard this buzzing
coming from the trees.
There must be dangerous insects up there.
Thanks for the information, Ulrich.
I’ll take care of it.
(MAN SCREAMING)
Help! Help! Get them off!
We’ll try to attract them to us!
Let’s go!
We’ve got to get him to the infirmary.
What about Ulrich?
He’ll take care of them.
Head that way! Hurry!
Hey, you’re…you’re hurt, Yumi.
Oh, it’s nothing serious, Ulrich.
Just a scratch.
Uh, I think we can go now.
Well?
Mister Bennett was lucky.
One more bite, and…
Yeah, that’s right,
but he’s still not in great shape.
The principal sent for help.
They’re gonna get rid of the nest.
I don’t know what you guys think, but I…
But you think it’s XANA.
Come on, cut it out.
Hornet’s nests have always been around,
and accidents happen all the time!
You’re right, but these hornets,
they were after us and nobody else.
Well, I say we check it out.
I’ll try to contact Aelita.
I’m going back to class,
but keep me posted.
Do you realize the damage
these bugs can cause?
There are thousands of them!
If XANA is in on this attack,
we could have a very
serious problem, huh?
Don’t you think so?
Hello!
Uh, what?
Uh, yeah! Right!
I mean, I don't know.
Ulrich, you wouldn’t
happen to have a crush
on this secret admirer
of yours, would you?
Hm, Ulrich?
Hm?
Yeah, you could be right.
(CLEARS THROAT)
What’s all this about me
being in love with Jim?
Uh…
Start that rumor again,
and even your dog
won’t recognize you!
Aelita, do you read me?
Loud and clear.
How are things in the real world?
We’ve got a problem.
And we think it might be XANA.
Have you noticed anything?
No. At least here in
the desert, things are calm.
But if you want I can
check out the other regions.
Good idea.
And in the meantime,
I’ll run a scan to see if
there’s an activated tower.
There it is.
Aelita, the scanner spotted
an activated tower in the forest
Okay. I’m in the forest now.
I’ll try to find it.
I’ll tell the others.
(RINGING)
Alert!
XANA has activated a tower,
and Aelita’s trying to find it, guys.
It looks as if something’s up.
Jeremie wants us to
go to the factory right now.
No--no, wait, Yumi.
I wanted to, uh,
to tell you something.
It’s about your…
about your letter.
Huh? But--
No, let me finish.
You said in the letter that…
that you had certain
feelings for me, and…
Huh?
I wanted you to know that…
that I feel the same thing for you.
There. I’ve said it.
But I never sent you any letter, Ulrich.
(LAUGHTER)
Oh, that has got to hurt!
Kind of embarrassing if you ask me!
(CACKLES)
Forget them. Don’t worry.
I don’t care. Leave me alone!
But…
Oh, no!
Oh, wow. Nice going, XANA.
Jeremie, any suggestions
would be very welcome.
Uh, get away from here
as fast as we can?
We’re trapped!
Hey, you got any other ideas?
Jump!
(COUGHING)
Come on.
This is your idea?
Insects are very sensitive to smells.
They’re not the only ones, huh?
Eugh.
Hey, I think it worked!
Looks like it.
What do you know?
What’s that smell?
Ask Jeremie.
We left you a message.
Didn’t you get it?
What do you think?
I didn’t feel like checking my messages.
Look, I think we should talk.
I know what you’re gonna tell me,
and I don’t wanna hear it.
Ulrich, this is all
on account of Sissi!
Don’t you think I know that?
But because of her, I’m confused.
Every time I see you,
I don’t know what to think.
So just leave me alone, okay?
He’s losing it.
Aelita?
Are you okay?
Yes, I found the activated tower.
But it’s guarded. I can’t access it.
Don’t worry. Help is on the way.
Hey, guys, hold on a minute!
The bugs have blocked
the factory entrance,
and I would rather
stay out of that sewer.
Don’t worry, Odd.
I’m way ahead of you on this one.
Well, what’s the deal?
(BEEPING)
Bingo!
Pretty clever, huh?
This thing generates ultrasounds
of about thirty thousand hertz.
Like all insects, hornets
are capable of receiving the--
Fascinating, but we
don’t have time, so let’s move!
(STUDENTS SCREAM)
Get inside!
Come on, hurry up!
Headquarters, we’ve got a problem.
We’re at the junior high school, right.
Your thing stopped! How come?
Battery’s dead.
What!?
Hurry up!
Okay, here we go.
Aelita, do you read me?
We’re on our way. Hang in there!
No time to lose. To the forest!
Transfer Ulrich.
Transfer Yumi.
Transfer Odd.
Hurry! Hurry!
Scanner Odd.
Scanner Ulrich.
Scanner Yumi.
Virtualization!
Come in, Aelita.
Aelita, answer me!
Oh, no. This cannot be happening!
Do you see her?
No, not yet.
Oh, and talk about
embarrassing situations,
I’m sure that Ulrich’s not about
to forget this for a long time.
What a genius I am!
You could say something.
A-a-a-aah!
Wait up!
Careful. Three swarms of
Hornets converging.
Get ready.
Laser arrow!
Less than 20 life points left, Yumi.
Be careful, Odd!
Odd, 80 life points left.
Ulrich, what are you doing?
Odd, two enemies at three o’clock!
Laser arrow!
Aelita!
No, Yumi! Aelita!
Aelita, are you okay?
Yes. I’m fine, Jeremie.
Yumi, in front of you!
Yeah!
Watch it! They’re coming back.
Yumi, you’ve only got
20 life points left.
Ulrich, wake up!
Odd!
Odd, you have hardly
any life points left.
Now!
(PANTING)
Ulrich, are you with us or not?
I know you’re unhappy,
but there’s no reason to be.
Our friendship’s
stronger than that, right?
You can’t let Sissi’s dirty tricks
break us up, can you?
So forget all about that,
please. We need your help!
You two head for the tower.
I’ll take care of them.
Well, it’s about time.
Triangulate!
Impact!
Yumi!
Oh, no!
Go on, Aelita!
Hiyah! Impact!
Ulrich, you’re the greatest.
(SCREAMING)
Aaah! Go away!
No, no! Help!
Return to the past now.
Uh…uh, hi!
Uh, I was just passing by, and I…
What do ya know?
Let’s see now.
It’s, uh…
Well, that’s a pretty
embarrassing situation,
don’t you think?
I, uh, this wasn’t the right door!
It sure isn’t!
Why not give it to Nicholas or Herb?
They’d be delighted!
(LAUGHS)
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO